{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2328","name":"DeAngelo's Soul Food Deli & More","address":"17425 Telegraph Rd","zipcode":"48219","owner":"DeAngelo & Renee Davis","licenseNumber":"050699","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.27760,42.41794","geojson":{"id":"2328","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.277603621,42.4179419380001]},"properties":{"name":"DeAngelo's Soul Food Deli & More","owner":"DeAngelo & Renee Davis","address":"17425 Telegraph Rd","zipcode":"48219","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"050699","establishmentid":"2328","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/20/2017"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1610","name":"Sun China Restaurant","address":"16901 Telegraph Rd"},{"establishmentid":"5115","name":"Farmer Kay Market","address":"24311 W McNichols Rd"},{"establishmentid":"327","name":"Toy Box II Bar and Grill, Inc.","address":"24351 W McNichols Rd"},{"establishmentid":"2342","name":"Bookie's Ham & Soul ","address":"23636 Grand River Ave"},{"establishmentid":"1086","name":"Rocky's Grill Coney Island","address":"24611 W McNichols Rd"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43342","inspectionDate":"2018-09-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hat","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"41570","inspectionDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"Longer than 7 days stored at 41 degrees f After preparation","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-02-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide proper date marks as stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"39627","inspectionDate":"2017-08-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37988","inspectionDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."}]},{"inspectionid":"36396","inspectionDate":"2016-09-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"outsides of equipment","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2328"}}